http://www.advanceinsurance.com/privacy.shtml

Skip Navigation
Employer Newsletters
Search Filled
Have a Question?
Your Privacy
At Advance Insurance Company of Kansas (AICK), we are committed to protecting your privacy. The information collected on our site is used strictly for expediting claims, enrollment forms and other related items on behalf of our customers and partners. We do not sell or trade any customer/partner data with any firm, for any reason.
What information do we collect? How do we use it?
When processing a claim and/or other documents, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, client/agent information and any other pertinent data. This allows us to process documents completely and accurately.
We use your username/password login information to personalize forms to your state and to ensure proper routing within AICK.
We will monitor traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop effective programs and content for our customers and partners.
We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the website, new services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable. If you would rather not receive this information, you may visit our site to remove yourself from our distribution list.
How does AICK protect customer information?
We follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information which you've given us, to prevent unauthorized access.
What about "cookies"?
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, but they do enable us to provide features to you between visits to our website. Most website browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can still use most of the features on our site, including using or downloading forms.
Will AICK disclose the information it collects to outside parties?
AICK does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. We may provide aggregate statistics about our customers; sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.
Your consent
By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Advance Insurance Company of Kansas. If change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
WARNING: Could not load HELPFUL RESOURCES
Legal Notices
Help
Privacy Policy
Blue Cross and Blue Shield of Kansas and Advance Insurance Company of Kansas
are Independent Licensees of the Blue Cross Blue Shield Association.
Blue Cross and Blue Shield of Kansas serves all counties in Kansas except Johnson and Wyandotte.
® Registered Trademarks of the Blue Cross Blue Shield Association.
If you have any questions or comments about this site, please notify our webmaster.
Top
